Guide to the National Guardian Photographs PHOTOS.213
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Mex-Americans, 1976-1976 (Box 30, Folder 20)
- Chicanos, 1969-1980 (Box 30, Folder 21)
- Dairy Farming, 1957-1957 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Blacks Rebel Miami Florida, undated (Box 31, Folder 2)
- Health Medicare, 1962-1966 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- Welfare, 1961-1977 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Urban Rebellions, 1967-1971 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Welfare (Economy-Domestic Conditions), 1966-1969 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Native Americans Housing/Unemployment, 1958-1974 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Native Americans Resistance, 1969-1979 (Box 31, Folder 8-10)
- Native Americans Graphics, 1978-1978 (Box 31, Folder 11)
- Native Americans Reactionaries/Support, 1957-1977 (Box 31, Folder 12)
- Police Brutality, 1985-1989 (Box 31, Folder 13)
- Labor and The Elections, 1938-1978 (Box 31, Folder 14-17)
- Labor and The Elections, 1938-1978 (Box 32, Folder 1-3)
- Latino Struggle, 1978-1980 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Black Panthers, 1968-1977 (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Black Panthers Party, 1966-1972 (Box 32, Folder 6)
- Panther Breakfast Program, 1967-1976 (Box 32, Folder 7)
- Black Panther Party – Political Trials, 1968-1970 (Box 32, Folder 8)
- Boston – Racist Attack, 1976-1976 (Box 32, Folder 9)
- Affirmative Action Bakke, 1977-1978 (Box 32, Folder 10)
- Civil Rights, 1957-1971 (Box 32, Folder 11)
- Civil Rights-Demonstrations, 1954-1969 (Box 32, Folder 12)
- Civil Rights Discrimination-Employment Strikes, 1963-1963 (Box 32, Folder 13)
- Black Muslims, 1962-1965 (Box 32, Folder 14)
- Little Rock, Arkansas, 1957-1958 (Box 32, Folder 15)
- Black Organizations, Miscellaneous – organizations and groups, 1967-1971 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Integration – Education – Charlotte, NC, Winston-Salem, Nashville, Tenn, San Antonio, Texas, Virginia, NYC NY, Freeport LI, Florida, Boston, Mass, San Francisco, Calif – School Integration from "TENDER WARRIORS", 1957-1958 (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Civil Rights – Liberties Tallahassee, Florida Rape of 19 Year Old Negro Coed, 1959-1959 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- Chaney-Goodman-Schwerner, 1964-1964 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Civil Liberties – Discrimination Pilgrimage to Washington, D.C., 1957-1957 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- Black Struggle, 1961-1961 (Box 33, Folder 6)
- Black Struggle Old Photos, 1953-1962 (Box 33, Folder 7)
- Till, Emmitt Louis Till Murder, 1955-1956 (Box 33, Folder 8)
- Black Struggle Civil Rights, 1957-1959 (Box 33, Folder 9)
- Civil Rights US Civil Rights Commission, 1958-1959 (Box 33, Folder 10)
- Black Struggle, 1960-1960 (Box 33, Folder 43051)
- Civil Rights – Monroe, North Carolina "KISSING CASE": David Fuzzy" Simpson and Hanover Thompson, Mrs. Jennie Simpson, Mrs. Evelyn Thompson, Dr. A. E. Perry, Robert F. Williams, Mrs. Mary Ruth Reid Assault Case, Rev TH Harris, 1950-1960 (Box 33, Folder 13)
- Malcolm X March in Brooklyn, 1986-1986 (Box 33, Folder 14)
- Black Struggle Civil Rights – 1963, 1963-1963 (Box 33, Folder 15)
- Demonstrations – Anti-Klan, 1986-1988 (Box 33, Folder 16)
- Demonstrations – Labor, 1986-1986 (Box 33, Folder 17)
- Demonstrations – Labor, 1981-1988 (Box 33, Folder 18-19)
- Demonstrations – Mexico, 1988-1988 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Labor Day, 1988-1988 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Demonstrations Libya, 1986-1986 (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Demonstrations – Grenada, 1983-1983 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Demonstrations – Irish Support, 1981-1983 (Box 34, Folder 5)
- Palestine Demonstrations, 1988-1988 (Box 34, Folder 6)
- LA8 – Palestinians, 1987-1987 (Box 34, Folder 7)
- Demonstrations – Lebanon and other Mideast, 1975-1988 (Box 34, Folder 42956)
- Demonstrations – Poland (Domestic – International), 1980-1984 (Box 34, Folder 10)
- Demonstrations – Parks, 1989-1989 (Box 34, Folder 11)
- Demonstrations – Prison, 1988-1989 (Box 34, Folder 12)
- Tompkins Square Park Demo, 1986-1989 (Box 34, Folder 13)
- Demonstrations – Pollution, 1986-1988 (Box 34, Folder 14)
- Persian Gulf Protests, etc., 1988-1988 (Box 34, Folder 15)
- Racism, skinhead, 1989-1989 (Box 34, Folder 16)
- Racism Demonstrations, 1986-1988 (Box 34, Folder 17-18)
- Demonstrations – Rate Hikes, 1987-1987 (Box 34, Folder 19)
- EPA Miscellaneous, 1984-1988 (Box 34, Folder 20)
- Demonstrations – Old Age, Social Security, 1985-1985 (Box 34, Folder 21)
- Rape Demonstrations, 1988-1988 (Box 34, Folder 22)
- Sanctuary, 1984-1986 (Box 34, Folder 23)
- Demonstrations Seabrook, 1986-1987 (Box 34, Folder 24)
- Demo Union Carbide, 1984-1984 (Box 34, Folder 25)
- Demonstrations – Veterans, 1982-1987 (Box 34, Folder 26)
- Vietnam Vets, 1985-1986 (Box 34, Folder 27)
- Wilson/Train wreck and subsequent Demonstrations, 1987-1988 (Box 35, Folder 1)
- Gentrification, 1985-1985 (Box 35, Folder 2)
- Homelessness, 1982-1987 (Box 35, Folder 42798)
- Famine, 1984-1985 (Box 35, Folder 5)
- Freeway Hall Case Seattle Sociologist, 1975-1985 (Box 35, Folder 6)
- Family, 1985-1985 (Box 35, Folder 7)
- Feminist, 1987-1987 (Box 35, Folder 8)
- Food, 1985-1985 (Box 35, Folder 9)
- Food and Central America Conference, 1985-1985 (Box 35, Folder 10)
- Farms, 1984-1989 (Box 35, Folder 11)
- Freeze, Salt, Talks, etc., 1982-1983 (Box 35, Folder 12)
- Former Officials, 1980-1985 (Box 35, Folder 13-14)
- Great Peace March, 1986-1986 (Box 35, Folder 15)
- Gambling and Lotteries, 1985-1985 (Box 35, Folder 16)
- Gay and Lesbian, 1982-1986 (Box 35, Folder 17)
- Gay and Lesbian Movement, 1984-1985 (Box 35, Folder 18)
- Genetics, 1987-1987 (Box 35, Folder 19)
- Gramm-Rudman, 1986-1987 (Box 35, Folder 20)
- Greenpeace, 1983-1993 (Box 35, Folder 21)
- Grey Panthers, 1981-1985 (Box 36, Folder 1)
- Guns/Control, 1989-1989 (Box 36, Folder 2)
- Guardian Angels, 1983-1983 (Box 36, Folder 3)
- Harlem, 1985-1986 (Box 36, Folder 4)
- Hard Times, 1971-1982 (Box 36, Folder 5)
- Health and Hospital, 1989-1989 (Box 36, Folder 6)
- High Tec, undated (Box 36, Folder 7)
- Heritage Conservations, undated (Box 36, Folder 8)
- Homeless, 1989-1990 (Box 36, Folder 9)
- Homeless, 1989-1989 (Box 36, Folder 10)
- Homeless Rallies, etc., 1983-1989 (Box 36, Folder 11)
- Housing, 1982-1985 (Box 36, Folder 12)
- A bat [(?)] New York 12 Shelter, 1985-1986 (Box 36, Folder 13)
- [Homeless], 1979-1988 (Box 36, Folder 14)
- Housing/Homeless, 1988-1988 (Box 36, Folder 15)
- Hunger, 1982-1987 (Box 36, Folder 16)
- Health, 1982-1989 (Box 36, Folder 17-18)
- Housing Demonstrations, 1977-1989 (Box 36, Folder 19)
- Housing, 1976-1989 (Box 36, Folder 20-21)
- HUD, 1989-1989 (Box 36, Folder 22)
- Demo Philippines, 1986-1988 (Box 36, Folder 23)
- Industry, 1982-1985 (Box 36, Folder 24)
- Jesse Jackson Campaign, 1980-1985 (Box 36, Folder 25)
- [Japanese Americans], 1981-1981 (Box 36, Folder 26)
- [Immigration], 1979-1986 (Box 37, Folder 1)
- Incineration, 1985-1988 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- Iran/Contra Scandal, 1986-1989 (Box 37, Folder 3)
- Ollie North and Friends, 1987-1987 (Box 37, Folder 4)
- Ollie North, 1985-1988 (Box 37, Folder 5)
- Immigration – INS see also Refugees, 1984-1989 (Box 37, Folder 6)
- Housing [Oversize], 1986-1986 (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Immigration Refugees Sanctuary, 1979-1986 (Box 37, Folder 8)
- Filipinos in U.S., 1986-1986 (Box 37, Folder 9)
- Klan, Nazis, Avowed Racists, 1976-1990 (Box 37, Folder 43019)
- Labor – Picket Lines, 1974-1985 (Box 37, Folder 12)
- Columbia, 1984-1985 (Box 37, Folder 13)
- Labor – Phelps Dodge, 1984-1984 (Box 37, Folder 14)
- Labor Picket – Hotel Workers, 1985-1985 (Box 37, Folder 15)
- Latinos, 1982-1983 (Box 37, Folder 16)
- Law and Order, 1981-1985 (Box 37, Folder 17)
- Leadership – Left, 1982-1989 (Box 37, Folder 18)
- Leaders – Latino, 1976-1976 (Box 38, Folder 1)
- Leaders – Business, 1981-1985 (Box 38, Folder 2)
- Leaders – Women, 1980-1985 (Box 38, Folder 3)
- Left Groups, 1979-1987 (Box 38, Folder 4)
- Legal Aid, 1987-1987 (Box 38, Folder 5)
- Martin Luther King Day Parades, etc., 1988-1988 (Box 38, Folder 6)
- Medicare, 1985-1985 (Box 38, Folder 7)
- Media People – Celebs, 1982-1985 (Box 38, Folder 42956)
- Media Scand[al]s, 1987-1987 (Box 38, Folder 10)
- Medicine, 1985-1985 (Box 38, Folder 11)
- Migrant Workers, 1982-1983 (Box 38, Folder 12)
- Nuke Energy, 1979-1986 (Box 38, Folder 13)
- Occupational Safety and Health, 1977-1987 (Box 38, Folder 14)
- Nuclear Weapons Demonstrations, 1984-1989 (Box 38, Folder 15)
- [New Bedford], undated (Box 38, Folder 16)
- Nature Miscellaneous and Natural Disasters, 1989-1989 (Box 38, Folder 17)
- American Indians, 1985-1985 (Box 38, Folder 18)
- Native Americans, 1979-1988 (Box 38, Folder 19)
- New Right, 1982-1985 (Box 38, Folder 20)
- National Rifle Association, 1986-1986 (Box 39, Folder 1)
- Native Americans, 1958-1988 (Box 39, Folder 42769)
- "MOVE", 1985-1986 (Box 39, Folder 4)
- Moonies, 1981-1986 (Box 39, Folder 5)
- Minimum Wage, 1989-1989 (Box 39, Folder 6)
- Mobster, Gambling, Underground, 1983-1983 (Box 39, Folder 7)
- Mining, 1984-1985 (Box 39, Folder 8)
- Weapons, 1985-1989 (Box 39, Folder 9)
- Military Hardware and War Games, 1980-1989 (Box 39, Folder 43019)
- New York City, 1984-1989 (Box 39, Folder 12)
- Military Mugs Miscellaneous, 1981-1989 (Box 39, Folder 13)
- Planned Parenthood, 1981-1981 (Box 39, Folder 14)
- Racism, 1986-1987 (Box 39, Folder 15)
- Political Prisoners, 1987-1989 (Box 39, Folder 16)
- Poverty Programs/Cutbacks, 1976-1983 (Box 39, Folder 17)
- Political Trials, 1981-1989 (Box 39, Folder 18)
- Pope/Religion, 1982-1987 (Box 39, Folder 19)
- Porn, 1984-1986 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Politicians, 1980-1984 (Box 40, Folder 2)
- Prisons, 1982-1989 (Box 40, Folder 3)
- [Green River Murders], 1985-1985 (Box 40, Folder 4)
- Public Works, 1983-1983 (Box 40, Folder 5)
- Puerto Rican Nationalists, 1979-1979 (Box 40, Folder 6)
- Radiation, undated (Box 40, Folder 7)
- Rainbow, 1988-1990 (Box 40, Folder 8)
- Rape, 1982-1985 (Box 40, Folder 9)
- Upstate Racism, 1988-1988 (Box 40, Folder 10)
- Reagan Administration --Attorney General and Justice Meese, Turner, Reynolds, 1982-1987 (Box 40, Folder 11)
- Reagan Administration -- Ambassadors, 1981-1985 (Box 40, Folder 12)
- Reagan Administration --Agriculture, 1980-1983 (Box 40, Folder 13)
- Reagan Administration -- Chief of Staff, 1981-1985 (Box 40, Folder 14)
- Reagan Administration -- CIA – Casey, 1986-1986 (Box 40, Folder 15)
- Reagan Administration -- Defense, 1981-1985 (Box 40, Folder 16)
- Reagan Administration -- Commerce, 1982-1985 (Box 40, Folder 17)
- Reagan Administration -- Education, 1985-1986 (Box 40, Folder 18)
- Reagan Administration -- Energy, 1980-1985 (Box 40, Folder 19)
- Reagan Administration -- Health and Human Services, 1981-1983 (Box 40, Folder 20)
- Reagan Administration -- Budget, 1981-1985 (Box 40, Folder 21)
- Reagan Administration -- EPA, 1981-1983 (Box 40, Folder 22)
- Reagan Administration -- Federal Reserve, 1980-1985 (Box 40, Folder 23)
- Reagan Administration -- FTC, 1981-1981 (Box 40, Folder 24)
- Reagan Administration -- Interior, 1981-1983 (Box 40, Folder 25)
- Reagan Administration -- Housing and Urban Development HUD, 1980-1983 (Box 40, Folder 26)
- Reagan Administration -- Labor, 1981-1982 (Box 40, Folder 27)
- Reagan Administration -- McFarlane, 1984-1985 (Box 40, Folder 28)
- Reagan Administration -- Press Secretary, 1981-1987 (Box 40, Folder 29)
- Reagan Administration -- Vice President Bush, 1980-1985 (Box 40, Folder 30)
- Reagan Administration -- Transportation, 1981-1983 (Box 40, Folder 31)
- Reagan Administration -- Secretary of State, 1981-1987 (Box 40, Folder 32)
- Reagan Administration -- Treasury, 1981-1985 (Box 40, Folder 33)
- Reagan Administration -- Miscellaneous, 1981-1986 (Box 40, Folder 34)
- Repression: CIA, FBI, Police, Immigration Justice, 1950-1985 (Box 40, Folder 35)
- Refugees outside U.S./ Miscellaneous, 1985-1989 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- Republicans, 1981-1985 (Box 41, Folder 2)
- Repression, 1982-1984 (Box 41, Folder 3)
- Red-Baiting, 1953-1985 (Box 41, Folder 4)
- Religion, 1982-1986 (Box 41, Folder 5)
- [Peace], 1983-1985 (Box 41, Folder 6)
- Refugees outside U.S./ Haiti, 1981-1985 (Box 41, Folder 7)
- Refugees, Illegal Aliens, Immigrants, 1981-1988 (Box 41, Folder 8)
- Demonstrations – Women, 1971-1984 (Box 41, Folder 9)
- Women-Equal + Abortion Rights Demonstrations, 1970-1988 (Box 41, Folder 10)
- Women â™€-Jobs (usual + unusual) + Personalities, 1969-1976 (Box 41, Folder 43051)
- Women in Government, undated (Box 42, Folder 13)
- Puerto Rico, 1977-1979 (Box 42, Folder 14)
- FALN, 1977-1980 (Box 42, Folder 15)
- Democratic Convention, 1968-1968 (Box 42, Folder 16)
- Peace Resistance 1968, 1968-1968 (Box 42, Folder 17)
- Disarmament, 1962-1978 (Box 42, Folder 18)
- Birth Control, 1969-1971 (Box 42, Folder 19)
- Housing, 1964-1976 (Box 42, Folder 20)
- Gay Struggle, 1977-1979 (Box 42, Folder 21)
- Gay Rights, 1979-1979 (Box 42, Folder 22)
- U.S. Capitalism Graphics, 1968-1979 (Box 42, Folder 23-26)
- U.S. Imperialism Graphics, 1970-1979 (Box 42, Folder 27)
- Chile – Demonstrations in U.S., 1973-1977 (Box 43, Folder 1)
- Salt II, 1979-1979 (Box 43, Folder 2)
- Farm Workers and Chicanos, 1976-1979 (Box 43, Folder 3)
- U.S. Capitalism-Photos, 1941-1978 (Box 43, Folder 4)
- U.S. Capitalism, 1976-1979 (Box 43, Folder 5)
- Cutbacks – NYC, 1971-1977 (Box 43, Folder 6)
- People's and Democratic Conventions NYC, 1980-1980 (Box 43, Folder 7)
- 1929 Crash, 1945-1979 (Box 43, Folder 8)
- [Strikes], 1978-1979 (Box 43, Folder 9)
- Strikes, 1979-1979 (Box 43, Folder 10)
- Busing, 1974-1976 (Box 43, Folder 43051)
- Senior Citizens, 1935-1974 (Box 43, Folder 13)
- Cartoons, etc., 1977-1978 (Box 43, Folder 14)
- Arms Control, 1977-1977 (Box 44, Folder 1)
- Day Care, 1973-1976 (Box 44, Folder 2)
- Inflation, 1966-1978 (Box 44, Folder 3)
- Asians Struggle/U.S., 1978-1978 (Box 44, Folder 4)
- Workers, 1978-1978 (Box 44, Folder 5)
- Refugees – Exiles, Concentration Camp Victims, etc., 1953-1969 (Box 44, Folder 6)
- Busing (Boston, etc.), 1971-1976 (Box 44, Folder 7)
- Busing, 1971-1977 (Box 44, Folder 8)
- Immigration, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 9)
- Poverty – U.S. Minorities, 1966-1976 (Box 44, Folder 10)
- Jimmy Carter, 1976-1979 (Box 44, Folder 11)
- Campaign - 1976, 1976-1976 (Box 44, Folder 12)
- Education, 1970-1980 (Box 44, Folder 13)
- Teaching Equipment and Methods, 1960-1979 (Box 44, Folder 14)
- NYC Crisis, 1975-1975 (Box 44, Folder 15)
- U.S. Congress, 1974-1975 (Box 44, Folder 16)
- U.S Bicentennial, 1976-1976 (Box 44, Folder 17)
- International Hotel Demonstrations S.F., 1977-1977 (Box 44, Folder 18)
- Peace Corp, 1961-1968 (Box 44, Folder 19)
- Chinese, 1970-1979 (Box 44, Folder 20)
- Right Wingers, 1961-1978 (Box 44, Folder 21)
- Bombings, 1967-1971 (Box 44, Folder 22)
- "Human Rights", 1977-1977 (Box 44, Folder 23)
- Commissions [Warren], 1964-1975 (Box 44, Folder 24)
- UN Meeting and International Politics, 1954-1975 (Box 44, Folder 25)
- National Black Convention, 1971-1972 (Box 44, Folder 26)
- Poverty – U.S. Whites, 1949-1976 (Box 44, Folder 27)
- U.S. Support Demonstrations – PLO, 1976-1978 (Box 44, Folder 28)
- U.S. Support Demonstrations – Africa, 1977-1977 (Box 45, Folder 1)
- Misc. Demonstrat[ions], 1960-1971 (Box 45, Folder 2)
- U.S. Support Demonstrations – Iran, 1978-1979 (Box 45, Folder 3)
- U.S. Support Demonstrations – Asia, 1977-1979 (Box 45, Folder 4)
- U.S. Support Demonstrations – Latin America, 1978-1979 (Box 45, Folder 5)
- Cutback Demonstrations, 1974-1979 (Box 45, Folder 6)
- Sports Olympics, 1952-1968 (Box 45, Folder 7)
- Peoples Struggles-Democratic Freedom/Peace/Community Control, 1979-1979 (Box 45, Folder 8)
- Sports, 1978-1978 (Box 45, Folder 9)
- Sports, 1951-1987 (Box 45, Folder 10)
- Teachers, 1959-1987 (Box 45, Folder 11-14)
- Transit Striker – NYC, 1966-1966 (Box 45, Folder 15)
- Transit – Bus, Truck, Taxi, Subway, 1954-1976 (Box 45, Folder 16-17)
- Transit – Bus, Truck, Taxi, Subway, 1954-1976 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Teamsters/TDU, 1959-1982 (Box 46, Folder 42769)
- TWU STK, 1980-1980 (Box 46, Folder 4)
- Unemployment, 1963-1983 (Box 46, Folder 42861)
- Unemployment, 1981-1985 (Box 46, Folder 7)
- University Workers, undated (Box 46, Folder 8)
- World Federation of Trade Unions (Industry and Labor), 1985-1985 (Box 46, Folder 9)
- Corporate Heads and Executives (Industry and Labor), 1961-1969 (Box 46, Folder 10)
- Facilities Industry – Factories, 1959-1965 (Box 46, Folder 11)
- George Meany, 1955-1978 (Box 46, Folder 43082)
- "Movie Salt of the Earth Film of the Striking Miners of New Mexico", 1965-1965 (Box 47, Folder 1)
- Workers, 1976-1980 (Box 47, Folder 2-3)
- China Agriculture, 1958-1976 (Box 47, Folder 4)
- China, 1941-1974 (Box 47, Folder 5-8)
- China cont., 1971-1975 (Box 47, Folder 9-12)
- China cont., 1971-1975 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- China, 1933-1976 (Box 48, Folder 2-7)
- Bombing of Dru, 1960-1974 (Box 48, Folder 8-9)
- Cambodia Places, 1973-1978 (Box 50, Folder 2)
- [Cambodia], 1973-1973 (Box 50, Folder 3)
- Laos-Cambodian Conflict (late '70s) Chinese-Vietnamese Conflict (late '70s) etc., 1978-1979 (Box 48, Folder 10-12)
- Cambodia, 1973-1979 (Box 48, Folder 13)
- Cambodia Civilians (Casualties and Other), 1964-1980 (Box 48, Folder 14)
- Khmer Rouge, 1979-1979 (Box 48, Folder 15)
- Vietnamese People After Liberation, 1978-1985 (Box 48, Folder 16)
- Unemployed, 1984-1988 (Box 48, Folder 17)
- [Oversized Photos], 1982-1989 (Box 49, Folder 1-2)
- [Oversized Photos], 1982-1989 (Box 50, Folder 4)
- [Illustrated published materials most likely used for photograph research], 1965-1989 (Box 49, Folder 3-6)
- [Illustrated published materials most likely used for photograph research], 1965-1989 (Box 50, Folder 5-7)
- North Korea, 1982-1982 (Box 49, Folder 7)
- Original Artwork "Our Roots Are Still Alive", 1947-1968 (Box 51, Folder 12-14)
- Hugo Gellert Artwork, 1981-1981 (Box 51, Folder 9-10)
- Oversized photos, undated (Box 51, Folder 5)
- Record album covers, book covers, and related graphics, undated (Box 51, Folder 7-8)
- Oversized cartoons (some originals) and graphics, undated (Box 51, Folder 11)
- Collages and created graphics, undated (Box 51, Folder 2-4)
- Book Art MP, undated (Box 49, Folder 8-9)
- Book Art MP, 1983-1983 (Box 50, Folder 8)
- Poster Art MP, 1983-1983 (Box 50, Folder 9)
- Poster Art MP, 1983-1983 (Box 52, Folder 2)
- Glossies: Products, Special Boxes, Records, 1983-1983 (Box 52, Folder 2)
- Montor Records Graphics, 1979-1980 (Box 51, Folder 11)
- Children Under Apartheid, A portable photographic exhibition produced by International Defence and Aid Fund for Southern Africa in co-operation with United Nations Centre Against Apartheid for International Year of the Child, 1982-1982 (Box 51, Folder 15)
- [Trade For Peace Inc. Photos], 1979-1979 (Box 51, Folder 6)
- Africa, 1989-1989 (Box 51, Folder 1)
- [Illustrated published materials most likely used for photograph research], undated (Box 52, Folder 4-6)
- MP Records, 1967-1988 (Box 52, Folder 7)
- Book Covers, undated (Box 52, Folder 8-9)
- Book Covers, 1975-1982 (Box 53, Folder 1)
- Marketplace Veloxes, 1975-1982 (Box 53, Folder 42769)
- Book Covers, undated (Box 53, Folder 4)
- Marketplace Copies, 1974-1984 (Box 53, Folder 5)
- Product Art MP, 1981-1981 (Box 53, Folder 42893)
- MP Posters, 1983-1983 (Box 53, Folder 8)
- [Artist Renditions], 1975-1985 (Box 53, Folder 9)
- Feggo, 1979-1979 (Box 53, Folder 10)
- Christopher Temptander, undated (Box 53, Folder 11)
- MP: Art for Special Boxes Section, 1973-1973 (Box 54, Folder 1)
- [Ethiopian Negatives], 1979-1980 (Box 54, Folder 2)
- [Libya Negatives], 1976-1986 (Box 54, Folder 3)
- [Anti-Nuclear Negatives], 1980-1980 (Box 54, Folder 4)
- [Negatives-Elias Avoub and Harlem Protest of Atlanta Murders], undated (Box 54, Folder 5)
- [Demonstration in front of British Consulate and Anti-Klan Conference], 1981-1981 (Box 54, Folder 6)
- [Young Americans for Freedom Negatives], 1980-1981 (Box 54, Folder 7)
- Manila Folder titled "Bob" contains unidentifiable negatives, undated (Box 54, Folder 8)
- Military, undated (Box 54, Folder 9)
- [Anti-Imperialist Contingent Negatives], 1981-1981 (Box 54, Folder 10)
- Women In Army, undated (Box 54, Folder 11)
- Agent Orange, 1966-1973 (Box 54, Folder 12)
- [Negatives-University Club El Salvador and Guardian Sustainer Party], undated (Box 54, Folder 13)
- [Negatives-Sustainer Party and Demo NYC Fort Apache: The Bronx Movie], 1980-1980 (Box 54, Folder 14)
- [Eritrea, EPLF Soldiers and "We Won't Pay! We Won't Pay!" An Anti-Inflation Comedy], 1980-1980 (Box 54, Folder 15)
- [Historical Temperence Movement, EPLF and Eritrea], 1979-1979 (Box 54, Folder 16)
- [Board of Education and Integration Demonstrations], 1975-1981 (Box 54, Folder 17)
- Anti-Apartheid Rally D.C., 1963-1981 (Box 54, Folder 18)
- [Labor, Immigration, Women Demonstrations], 1987-1987 (Box 54, Folder 19)
- [Demonstrations-Iranian Students, Fort Apache, El Salvador, Solidarity Day Etc.], 1979-1981 (Box 54, Folder 20)
- [Cutbacks Protests, Memorial March Gene Viernes, Ethiopia, Etc.], 1979-1981 (Box 54, Folder 21)
- [Demonstrations-Anti-Racism Violence], 1976-1981 (Box 54, Folder 22)
- [Miscellaneous Protests and Demonstrations], 1981-1981 (Box 54, Folder 23-24)
- [Color Slides], 1954-1981 (Box 55, Folder 1)
- [Graphics Maps], 1973-1979 (Box 55, Folder 2)
- [Cartoons], 1976-1976 (Box 55, Folder 3)
- Military-Industrial Complex, 1984-1987 (Box 55, Folder 4)
- Documentary of Vietnam, 1968-1968 (Box 55, Folder 5)
- Nixon Era Graphics, 1940-1975 (Box 55, Folder 6)
- Cambodia Soldiers, 1968-1973 (Box 55, Folder 7-10)
- Kampuchea, 1970-1976 (Box 55, Folder 11-12)
- Kampuchea, 1970-1975 (Box 56, Folder 1)
- Phnom Penh, 1970-1975 (Box 56, Folder 2)
- Vietnam – Mugs, 1970-1979 (Box 56, Folder 42798)
- Vietnam – Militia/ Army, 1976-1977 (Box 56, Folder 5)
- Vietnam – Medicine, 1975-1977 (Box 56, Folder 6)
- Vietnam – Education, 1975-1978 (Box 56, Folder 42924)
- Vietnam – Scars of War, 1975-1977 (Box 56, Folder 9)
- Vietnam – Elections, 1973-1976 (Box 56, Folder 43019)
- Vietnam – Industry, 1976-1976 (Box 56, Folder 43082)
- Vietnam/Kampuchea/China Changes in Economy, 1975-1978 (Box 56, Folder 14)
- Vietnam – Agriculture Forestry/ Dairy/ Fishing, 1977-1978 (Box 56, Folder 15)
- Vietnam – Scenes, 1971-1978 (Box 57, Folder 1)
- Vietnam – Art/Culture, 1976-1978 (Box 57, Folder 2)
- Reconstruction – General, 1975-1978 (Box 57, Folder 42798)
- Vietnam – Children, 1975-1977 (Box 57, Folder 5)
- Vietnam – Sports, 1975-1977 (Box 57, Folder 6)
- Vietnamese in U.S., 1976-1976 (Box 57, Folder 7)
- Vietnam – National Celebrations Congresses, Meetings, etc., 1977-1977 (Box 57, Folder 42956)
- Vietnam – Liberation, 1975-1978 (Box 57, Folder 10)
- Women, 1973-1975 (Box 57, Folder 11)
- Vietnam, 1976-1977 (Box 57, Folder 12-17)
- Foreign Politicians, 1961-1976 (Box 58, Folder 1-3)
- The G.I. in Action before the Vietnamese Liberation, 1966-1973 (Box 58, Folder 4-5)
- South Vietnamese Politicians During U.S. Aggressive War, 1962-1975 (Box 58, Folder 6-7)
- The U.S. Air-bases in South Vietnam, 1957-1975 (Box 58, Folder 8-10)
- The U.S. Weapons in South Vietnam, 1963-1973 (Box 59, Folder 1-3)
- Women, 1967-1972 (Box 59, Folder 4)
- Vietnam, 1966-1979 (Box 59, Folder 5-7)
- Way of Life S. Vietnam, 1954-1975 (Box 59, Folder 42963)
- Medical Care S. Vietnam, 1962-1978 (Box 60, Folder 1)
- Anti-U.S. Air Graft During War, 1966-1973 (Box 60, Folder 2)
- Agriculture During War, 1966-1975 (Box 60, Folder 3)
- Children During War, 1970-1975 (Box 60, Folder 4)
- Construction and Way of Life During War, 1967-1974 (Box 60, Folder 42861)
- Culture During War, 1966-1975 (Box 60, Folder 7)
- Industry During War, 1971-1975 (Box 60, Folder 8)
- Medical Care During War, 1966-1975 (Box 60, Folder 9)
- Women During War, 1966-1975 (Box 60, Folder 10)
- Politic During War, 1967-1975 (Box 61, Folder 1)
- N. Vietnamese Politician During War, 1969-1975 (Box 61, Folder 2-3)
- Uncle Ho Chi Minh, 1966-1976 (Box 61, Folder 4)
- U.S. Prisoner in N. Vietnam During War, 1950-1975 (Box 61, Folder 5)
- Education During War, 1966-1975 (Box 61, Folder 6)